

Name: Ivan Stesic

Born: 01.10.1991.

Current Location: Belgrade
Current Employer: Freelancing

Web Portfolio, Linkedin, GitHub

Position: Front end developer

Email: ivan.stesic@gmail.com

Mobile Phone Number: +38169 55 10 991

Dedicated highly motivated developer with more than 4 years of experience, focused to write highly maintainable and reliable code. Good problem solver, always ready for new challenges, learning new skills and practices in area of programming and IT. Very good communication skills, teamwork capabilities and work ethics. My aim is continuous improvement, acquiring new knowledge and experience, career advancement.

EXPERIENCE

• Symphony Digital Bg—Software engineer (Jun 2022 – May 2023)
Building web applications written in React/Typescript and Next.js/Typescript. Working on internal projects independently and also as part of an international team for client purposes.

• Greco Shared Services Center– Front end developer (March 2021 – Jun 2022)

Worked in medium size team following principles of Scrum methodology. Responsible for develop in-house web-based user interface.

• ThinkBig Development – Front end developer (July 2020 – March 2021) Responsible for the develop responsive, web-based user interfaces, participate in code reviews of pull requests, work and collaborate with the rest of the development team. Daily communication with the client and the rest of team.

 Saga New Frontier Group – Deployment engineer (March 2019 – July 2020)

My responsibilities were to analyze, develop, test and implement RPA solutions with the maintenance of existing ones and helping front end team on React projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript (es6+), React, Next.js, TypeScript, jQuery, React Native
- State Management: React Context, Redux/Redux-toolkit, zustand, recoil
- REST API, WebSocket, React-Query, Axios
- HTML5, XML, CSS3, SASS
- **styled-components, Material UI, Fluent UI**, Chakra UI, Tailwind CSS, Materialize, Bootstrap
- VSC, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket, Basecamp, Jira
- RPA tools SAP Intelligent RPA (Contextor), UiPath

PROJECTS

FRONTEND

- <u>- Web marketplace for electric vehicles</u>: Online web portal / marketplace for electric vehicles. The app is responsive and has two versions, React and Next.js. Main project features are Auth pages, blog posts integrated with Sanity, vehicle listings with proper filters, vehicle details, and an integrated payment checkout process. Technology stack:React.js/Next.js/TypeScript, Sanity, styled-components, React Context, react-hook-form, Plaid, etc.
- Realestate platform: The platform is a consumer destination, branded completely to the brokerage and Agent. It anchors consumers in a single place, allowing brokerages to deliver a seamlessly connected experience throughout the entire home ownership lifecycle: from living in a home and understanding its value, searching for their next home, streamlining the complexities of a current transaction, moving into a new home and back to living in their current home. Stack: React/Typescript, recoil, talkjs, styled-components.
- *Visitor registration*: An ios application that allows employees and visitors to register upon arrival in the hub. In just a few clicks employee is signed in to his hub whereas the visitor can select his host and write down his name. The app is written in React Native for ios tablet devices.
- *Visitor registration dashboard*: A dashboard app that provides admins with data about hub entries of employees and visitors. It includes a list of daily visits or a list of visits in the time span between chosen dates with statistic information. The app is written in React, login is implemented as "login with google" functionality, for state management zustand and React Context, Chakra for UI.
- **Document Management System**: In-house project with a lot of functionalities similar to Microsoft Outlook. Application is written in React.js/TypeScript, React Context is used for state management, React Tiny for a text editor.
- **Business Fleet Management**: In-house project for monitoring vehicle insurance and policies. Application is written in React.js/Typescript, Redux-Toolkit is used for state management.
- <u>Crupto betting platform</u>: The cryptocurrency-based platform, which allows customers to bet with Bitcoin, Ethereum and more, along with statistic, promotion, news sections. Build with Next.js, styled-component, React Context...
- Admin Panel: Admin B2B app for Gaming platform written in React.js. React-material.fusetheme is used for UI. Data is provided through a WebSocket connection. The state management is handled with Redux and Hooks, localization with i18next. React-hook-form and Yup.js takes care of project forms and validation. Otherdependencies: react-use, react-table, lodash, moment, suneditor-react, react-html-parser...
- **Project for HR company**: HR Application is project divided in two parts. First part is application for candidates, and the second is admin app for recruiters. Both parts are written in React.js/TypeScript with Material-UI framework. State data is managed with Context API and Hooks. Yup.js library along with react-hook-form are used for form validation and submission. Version control with GitLab. Other dependencies: axios,lodash,day.js, js-base64...

RPA

- Cash management: Unattended, fully automated processing of deposits from the Automatic Transfer Service (ATS) devices along with funds distribution to the related bank branches. Process encompasses denomination structure submission as well as daily reports generation. Process is automated on two bank platform, with two RPA tools (UiPath and SAP Intelligent RPA). This process is build on two bank platforms, with to RPA tools (UiPath, SAP Intelligent RPA)

• Stack Language: SAP Intelligent RPA ,UiPath , JS(ES5), Node.js, C#, XML

EDUCATION

- Belgrade Institute of Technology $\,$ Front-end bootcamp focusing on JavaScript, 400 hours of $\,$ lectures and practical work.
- Faculty of Agriculture Financial Management for Agribusiness Master degree

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Serbian (Native)
- English (Professional working)

PERSONAL CHARACTERISTICS

- Responsible, persistent , dedicated, communicative
- Team and individual work ability
- Flexible, always ready for learning new things and research